var quizes = [
  {
    question: "Which one of these are a boolen ?",
    correctAnswer: "0",
    possibleAnswers: ["True", "Table Tennis", "1", "ðŸ”¥"],
  },
  {
    question: "What does var do ?",
    correctAnswer: "2",
    possibleAnswers: [
      "Adds padding to a box",
      "Styles an element",
      "declare a variable to be used ",
      "Makes a word bold",
    ],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Where do you put your script link ?",
    correctAnswer: "1",
    possibleAnswers: [" In the script tag that you created ", "Before the closing body ", "In the header ", " No need its magic"],
    
  },
 // .......................
 {
  question:
    "In Javascript, how do you grab an element from the HTML ?",
  correctAnswer: "1",
  possibleAnswers: [" Element Grab ", "Query Selector ", "Append ", " Text content"],
  
},
{
  question: "How do you start a for loop function",
  correctAnswer: "0",
  possibleAnswers: ["for, var index, size, number", "for, var, length, size ", " var, for, number, size ", "index, for, console log, var"],

},

{
  question: "Where is the heart of the HTML",
  correctAnswer: "3",
  possibleAnswers: [
    "Script",
    "Header",
    "Heart ",
    "Body",
  ],
},

{
  question: "Which browser has console log",
  correctAnswer: "2",
  possibleAnswers: [
    "Explorer",
    "Wikki",
    "Chrome ",
    "Safari",
  ],
},
{
  question: "What will save you time coding your CSS",
  correctAnswer: "3",
  possibleAnswers: [
    "American Hackers Associations",
    "Bootcamp UCLA",
    "W3 school ",
    "Bootstrap",
  ],
},
// ..............
{
  question: "Where do you find your storage in inspect",
  correctAnswer: "3",
  possibleAnswers: [
    "Console log",
    "HTML",
    "Settings ",
    "Application",
  ],
},

{
  question: "How do you call a function",
  correctAnswer: "2",
  possibleAnswers: [
    "function brackets",
    "name of function",
    "name of fuction paranthesis ",
    "Bracets i",
  ],
},
{
  question: "What does HTML samentic ?",
  correctAnswer: "3",
  possibleAnswers: [
    "Creating coding languages that relate to the project",
    "Using an element other than P",
    "Div inside of a div ",
    "Using an element other than Div",
  ],
},
]




  
  
